ff
ッ フ
Uuuuuuuu
ゥ ゥゥ
U G Eh, do you need this?
ゥ G え、これ要るの?
Ahhhhhhhhhhh Doddo
ア ッ フゥゥゥゥゥゥゥゥゥゥゥゥ Doddo
A small thing.
ち っちゃい物の
You can move a little.
ちょっと動けるんだね
Amazing quantity value.
すごい量値は
It's you.
お前なんだよ
Wait a minute, you're a senpai.
ちょっと、ずるいっしょ、先輩だよ
It's okay, I'm not coming, I'm having fun.
いいよ、来なくて、楽しんでるのだから
It's very powerful, isn't it?
すごく力出るじゃないですか
You're a luxury, that's it.
お前、贅沢だよ、それが
Did you say that too?
お 前の口もしたの?
You asked well.
よくたがったね
Both are so cute.
両方ふさわっちゃだね
I hate you, you.
お 前、恨ましいな、お前
It's disgusting.
恨ましい
No?
ダメ?
Can I pour it over a cup?
一杯にかけちゃっていい?
You can't do it, you.
お前、ダメだよ、お前
Just do it, you.
そのままやっていいよ、お前
You guys are not good friends, you guys.
お前、仲はダメだぞ、お前
Are you not on good terms?
仲はダメですか?
You, I'm your friend.
お 前、仲はお前
I'll deal with it later.
俺が後で仲やるんだから
Naka can't stand it.
仲は堪えてきないです
We're no good together, you.
仲はダメだぞ、お前
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すっごい
I had a feeling.
気持ちがあった
A lot will come out.
いっぱい出てきます
Wash it off thoroughly, in the shower.
しっかり流してあげろよ、シャワーで
Rinse thoroughly.
し っかり流します
You can't do it, so don't put it out.
やっちゃダメだから、出しちゃダメだよ
I will never release it, absolutely.
絶対出さないです、絶
versus.
対
Because it felt good.
気 持ちよかったからさ
At first, it was soft, after all.
最初、柔らかいね、やっぱり
Give it to me.
あげろ
It might be naughty.
やらしいかも
You, you, you.
お前、お前、お前
お 前、 お前、お前
Down
下
below
を 下
I've been spilling it.
に、 こぼしてきてきた
Did you wash it off?
洗い流した?
do not have.
ない
Also, you, you, you.
また、お前、お前、お前
The skin is plump.
肌プリプリ
I like boobs.
おっぱい好きだわ
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
At first, we didn't get along.
最初、仲はダメだからさ
I don't like it.
気に入らない
Because I don't do anything.
何もしないからさ
My dad made me drink a lot.
お父さんにたくさん飲めちゃったからさ
Should I try being serious?
真面目してみていいかな
I deleted it, but what's going on here?
消しちゃったけどさ、 ここどうなってんの?
Give me a little leg.
ちょっと足さ、 あげてみ
hand.
て
Haven't you gotten used to it yet?
まだ 慣れちゃってない?
Yesterday, Seya-kun
昨日、せやくん
Let's play a prank again.
も もう一回、悪戯しようかな
Look, it's getting messy.
ほら、ぐっちゃぐちゃになってきたじゃん
I wonder if this will make its way to Japan.
これさ、 日本に入るんじゃないかな
It tastes like it.
イッチの味しちゃうよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I want you to lick my belly.
お腹を舐めてほしいよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Well, I did it earlier, but let's do it again.
さ あ、さっきしたけどさ、 もう一回、
It got smaller.
小さくなっちゃった
No, I just pumped it.
いや、ちょっと、 スポンプしちゃったぞ
No matter what you do, this is it,
どうしてもらっても、 これでさ、
Bush it.
ブッシュしてよ
Forced bokkimoshi.
強制ボッキモシ
No matter how many times I say something cute like this,
何回でもさ、 こんな可愛いこと、
Because I want to have fun.
イッチしたいから
This is impossible, bokki sauce.
これで無理無理、 ボッキソース
It just got a little big.
さっきさ、ちょっと でかくなっちゃった
Look at me, I'm going to make a cute face.
こっち見て、可愛い顔にしてそう
I'm going to cum inside you.
中出しちゃうね
Have you had a drink?
ちょっと、飲んじゃった?
It's my second time.
2回目だからね